你是个好警察  亚当
You're a good cop, Adam.
你抓坏蛋很在行
You're really good at catching bad guys.
但你还是和我共事
And yet--And yet you work right next to one
而我是芝加哥的恶人之一
of the worst men in Chicago.
我的事业全都建立在过界
A man who built his career crossing the line
和违法之事上
and breaking the law.
但你没办法逮捕我
And yet you can't catch a criminal?
你觉得你还能糊弄我多久
How long do you think you're gonna be able to jerk me around?
我把视频给你了
I gave you the video.
那场斗殴的视频
The video of the fight.
霍斯特德为了救一个孩子的命
That tap dance with Halstead punching a bystander
打了一个旁观者的视频吗
while he's trying to save a kid's life?
你说你想要
You told me you wanted something
过界的东西  那就过界了
that crossed the line-- that crossed the line.
你知道我费了多大劲才给你那视频吗
Do you know how hard it was for me to give that to you?
我说我要有关博伊特的东西
I told you I wanted something on Voight.
实际点的东西
Something actionable.
这我给不了
I can't give you what you want.
没办法
I can't.
你有办法
Yes, you will.
否则你姐姐就要进监狱了
Or your sister will go to jail,
而你的小外甥就不得不认识
and your little nephew will have to learn all the names
新的寄养兄弟们了
of his new foster brothers.
而且芝加哥腐败警察的典范
And the poster boy for corrupt police in Chicago
就不会是汉克·博伊特
will not be Hank Voight.
而是你了
That will be you.
你有24小时  否则我就搞臭你
You got 24 hours, or I will bury your ass.
海莉·厄普顿
20分钟后来见我
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我得去见一个人  工作上的事
I gotta go see a guy about a job.
安全工作
Security gig.
来  我们得庆祝
Come on. We have to celebrate.
-庆祝什么  -在一起两周
- Celebrate what? - Our two week anniversary.
我不能迟到
I can't be late.
瑞安  我有一个问题
So, Ryan, I have a question.
我今晚能再见到你吗
Am I seeing you again tonight?
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
当然能
Hell yeah.
翻译     小酸奶   西之   风城章鱼X   不高兴童鞋
很好  凯特琳
Good, Caitlin.
翻译     H小欠   小萝莉   pang   圈圈
你刚刚搬到这里吗
So, you just moved here?
对  就上周
Yeah, last week.
校对     圈圈
想给我女儿找一个好的队伍
Looking for a good league for my daughter.
这个队不错  教练很好  家长也不错
This is the one. Good coaches, good families.
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
你会喜欢邻居们的
You're gonna love this neighborhood.
加油  凯特琳  加油
Get in there, Caitlin! Go for it!
后期     8T
朱利安...
So, Julianne...
我听说你可以帮我牵线
I was told that you could hook me up.
总监     圈圈
什么
Excuse me?
我的背需要点东西
I just-- I need something for my back.
我出了车祸  背很疼
I got into a car accident, and I'm in a lot of pain.
你需要一个医生
It sounds like you need a doctor.
莎拉·瑞思告诉我你能帮忙
Sarah Rathe told me that you could help.
我有现金
I have cash.
-你要多少  -我能拿到多少
- How much do you need? - How much can I get?
苏  我得帮帮我们的新邻居
Hey, Sue, I need to help out our new neighbor.
你能帮我带迪兰和凯特琳回家吗
Would you mind dropping Dylan and Caitlin back at the house?
当然
Mm-hmm, sure.
-80美金一片  -很贵啊
- It's $80 a pill. - That's pretty high.
是真货  不是外国的垃圾货
It's real Oxy. None of that Chinese crap.
好吧
Okay.
-在这里等着  -等等  我一起去
- Wait here. - Wait, I'll just go with you.
不行  那人很谨慎
No, the guy's skittish.
别担心  我很快就回来
Don't worry. I'll be right back.
-你听到了吗  -听到了
- Did you copy that? - Yeah.
已经到位
Already in the location.
好
Yeah, okay.
我盯着  我跟着她  海莉
I got the eye. I'll stay with her, Hailey.
我们要在孩子面前抓她吗
So, we're gonna bust her in front of her kids?
你想告诉警长我们掏了1505块
Do you wanna tell Sarge we lost 1505 funds
还被一个家庭妇女给耍了吗
and got played by a soccer mom?
我不知道
I don't know.
锡那罗亚贩毒团伙之后  这些都是小巫见大巫
After the Sinaloan cartel, this feels like small potatoes.
上个月这个地区已经有17个人吸毒过量死亡了
17 ODs in this area in the last month.
-这是大巫了吧  -好吧  你先去
- Big potato. - All right, after you.
-救命啊  -救命  苏
- Help, help! - Somebody--Sue!
-救命  -快来人
- Help! - Please!
救命啊  来人啊
Somebody help! Please, somebody!
-救命  -我们妈妈在里面
- Help! - Our mom's inside!
她晕过去了
She won't wake up!
-她在哪  -救命
- Where is she? - Please!
她在浴室
She's in the bathroom!
我们是警察
We're police.
你们待在这里  别动  好吗
You guys stay here. Stay put, all right?
好了...
Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa. Okay, hey, hey, hey.
看着我...
Look at me, look at me, look at me!
我是杰·霍斯特德警探
This is Detective Jay Halstead.
警号51163
Badge number 51163.
我需要你们派一辆救护车
I need you guys to roll an ambo
来南凯勒街4222号
to 4222 South Keller.
这里有一名女性吸毒过量
We got a female overdose victim.
她失去...  你们别过来
She's conv-- Hey, guys, stay back!
-朱利安  -她抽搐得很厉害
- Julianne! - She's convulsing pretty bad.
快点派人过来
Send help quick.
我带他们出去
I'm gonna get them out of here.
朱利安
Hey, hey, hey! Julianne!
朱利安  清醒一点
Julianne, stay with me.
坚持住  朱利安
Stay with me, Julianne!
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第九集
她偷了我们的钱去买毒品
She stole our money to buy her fix.
看起来她是想在孩子回来之前
Looks like she was trying to get high
先嗨一把
before her kids got home.
我们发现了一把刮胡刀还有白色粉末
We found a straight razor and a white powder substance.
现场检测到了羟考酮
Field tested for Oxy.
她可能是用鼻吸的
She probably snorted it.
我们很努力了  没办法救回她
We tried like hell, we couldn't revive her.
你们试图买毒品的报告我们会压下来
We'll crack off a vice report on your attempt to buy.
把她的电话丢掉
Dump her phone.
她肯定联络了她的供货商
She must have reached out to her supplier.
-好  -你好  汉克
- All right. - Hello, Hank.
你好  丹尼
Hey, Denny.
他也联系你了吗
So he called you, too?
他  我是来查案子的
He? Just here working a case.
好吧  那就归你了
Good. Now you own it.
我没有明白
I'm not following.
本案的死者名叫朱利安·威尔斯
The victim in the case is Julianne Wells.
威尔斯法官的女儿
Daughter of the Honorable Judge Wells.
汤米·威尔斯
Tommy Wells?
没错
That's right.
一名白人法官的女儿
Daughter of a white judge.
鸦片危机终于要登上
The opioid crisis is finally going to hit front page
《论坛报》头条了
of the "Tribune."
要咖啡吗
Coffee?
-谢了  -没事
- Thanks. - Yeah.
和你男朋友怎么样了
How'd it work out with your boyfriend?
-不怎么样  -能解决吗
- Not great. - Can you fix it?
我觉得已经发展到
Yeah, I think it got broke in a way
无法解决的地步了
you can't really fix.
太糟糕了
That sucks.
你为团队做出了正确的选择
Well hey, you did right by the team.
你为博伊特做出了正确的选择  这很重要
You did right by Voight. That's something, right?
好了  伙计们
All right, guys.
朱利安·哈德森
Julianne Hudson.
离婚  有两个孩子
Divorced, mother of two.
这两年一直在进出戒瘾所
Been in and out of rehab for the past two years.
你根本不知道她是威尔斯法官的女儿吗
And you had no idea she was Judge Wells' daughter?
她的姓是哈德森  这是她的夫名
She's going by Hudson. It's her married name.
我们本来不知道她还会贩毒
We did know she's a small-time dealer.
有两名吸毒过量者说是她牵线的
Two of the ODs said she hooked them up with Oxy.
我们本来想通过她查到她的货源
We were flipping her to get her supplier.
听着  我和我的线人谈过了
Yeah, look, I talked to my C.I.S.
林肯公园帮人并不是毒贩团伙
This move into Lincoln Park is not the cartels.
是个新来的
It's a new player.
我们和缉毒组都不知道来头
Nobody on our radar or Narcotics'.
售卖合法的羟考酮药物
Pushing legit Oxy pills.
我们查了朱利安的手机
Well, we dumped Julianne's phone,
她吸毒过量前打的最后一通电话
and the last call she made before she OD'd
是打给文斯·威廉  32秒
was to a Vance Williams for 32 seconds.
我们对林肯公园的15名吸毒过量者都进行了调查
We ran muds and tolls on the 17 ODs in Lincoln Park.
有六人也给这个文斯打过电话
Six of them called this guy Vance, too.
查到了他的社保号码
Got his, uh, social security records.
过去九个月一直在沃尔科特烧烤工作
Been working at the Wolcott Grill the last nine months.
好  你们俩去找他谈谈
All right, so why don't you two go talk to him?
虽然是新人  但是套路还是一样
Listen, it's new turf, but it's the same game.
找到毒贩  放长线钓大鱼
Bust the dealers, flip the minnows into sharks.
收到
Copy that.
汤米·威尔斯当上法官之前
You know, before Tommy Wells was a judge,
他是个警察
he was a cop.
我们一起上过警校
We were in the Academy together.
他是个好警察
Good police.
为他讨回公道吧
Let's do him right.
父母不该偏爱任何一个孩子
Parent's not supposed to have favorites,
但我就是偏爱朱利安
but Julianne was my favorite.
她喜欢运动
She loved sports.
所以她伤到了膝盖
That's how she hurt her knee.
然后就动了手术
And then came the operations.
止痛药
The pain pills.
我这辈子把无数瘾君子关进了监狱
Spent my whole career throwing drug addicts in jail
而我的女儿却也抵挡不了诱惑
and my own daughter went down the rabbit hole.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
听着
Listen, uh...
我和丹尼·伍兹聊了两句
I talked to Denny Woods.
我们认为是吸毒导致死亡
We're gonna pursue a narcotics induced homicide.
如果你能给我们的调查一些方向...
So if you can point us in a direction...
我也很想
I really wish I could.
朱利安陷得越深  就越把自己孤立起来
The deeper in Julianne got, the more she isolated herself.
是我们的制药公司和我们的医生
It was our drug companies and our doctors
给我们推荐的
who got us hooked.
他们说这是药
They called it medicine.
是我们自己放出了这头怪兽
We unleashed this monster on ourselves.
她是我的小女儿
She was my little girl.
我几年前失去了我的儿子
I lost my son a few years ago.
痛苦不会消失
Pain doesn't go away.
当最终得到正义时  会感到些许宽慰
There is some consolation when justice is done.
会让内心的空洞浅一点
Makes the hole a little shallower.
我们会尽我们所能
We're gonna do everything we can.
好
Yeah.
All right.
这是意大利皮诺
Italian Pino grigio here.
-好吧  -清新可口
- Okay. - Crisp, dry.
柠檬酸橙味
A lot of lemon and lime.
余味还有点青苹果味
Even some green apple in the finish.
我觉得你会喜欢的
I think you're gonna like it.
没错  你很不错嘛  文斯
I do. You know your stuff, Vance.
-你在这里工作多久了  -没多久
- How long you worked here? - Not that long.
你已经小有名气了
And you've already made a name for yourself.
听说来找你就行了
I hear that you are the man to see.
不好意思  你叫什么来着
Sorry, tell me your name again?
戴安娜
Diana.
你想要什么  戴安娜
So, what do you want, Diana?
我想找点乐子
I want to have fun.
我想帮别人也找点乐子
And I want to help other people have fun.
我在一个网球俱乐部工作
See, I work at a tennis club.
有很多女人  很多空暇时间
There's a lot of women. A lot of free time.
没什么人盯着
Not a lot of supervision.
处女地啊  文斯  只不过没有处女
Virgin territory, Vance. Without the virgins.
继续说
I'm listening.
她们想开派对  但不想搞针筒什么的
They wanna party. They don't like the needles.
你喜欢派对吗
Do you like to party?
喜欢  但是
I do. But...
你知道我在哪里能搞到点羟考酮吗
Do you know where I can get some Oxy?
法官女儿出事后...
So, after that thing with the judge's daughter--
嗯
Yeah?
供货商会很低调
Suppliers are gonna be laying low.
-不过  -好的
- But... - Okay.
我藏了点备用
I have a recreational stash.
太好了
Sweet.
我十分钟后下班  会有时间
I'll be free in ten minutes.
其实吧  不会了
Actually, you won't be.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD.
-臭婊子  -注意点
- Bitch. - Hey.
-你还好吧  金  -没事
- You good, Kim? - I'm fine.
认识她吗
Know her?
我可能在酒吧见过她
I may have seen her at the bar.
因为你们老板说昨天才看见你和朱利安说话
'Cause your manager saw you talking to Julianne yesterday.
然后她就吸了600毫克的羟考酮
After which, she snorted 600 milligrams of OxyContin.
算我倒霉  但不能怨我
That's a bummer, but that's not on me.
因为你的备用货
'Cause your recreational stash,
和杀死朱利安的药片是一样的
same pills that killed Julianne.
-我要见律师  -你是本地人吗
- I want a lawyer. - You from Chicago?
跟这个有什么关系
What's that got to do with it?
-你是芝加哥人吗  -是  威尔米特的
- Are you from Chicago? - Yeah, Wilmette.
那你应该知道这里是怎么办事的
So then you know how this city works.
这可是法官的女儿
I mean, this--this is the daughter of a judge.
肯定要有人付出代价  是不是
So, someone's gonna pay for this, right?
换了我是你
I mean, if I were you,
我宁可让我的上线来顶锅
I'd wanna put it on my supplier.
不过  如果你想保护他
But if you wanna protect him,
我也很乐意抓你
I'm happy to go with you.
这就意味着所有责任都是你来担
And that means you'll take the full ride
整个谋杀罪名
for the homicide charge.
我倒有点希望他把这罪名顶了
You know, I kinda hope he eats it.
这样我们就能早点下班了
'Cause this means we get to go home early.
所以  你的上线是谁
So, who's your supplier?
最后机会  文斯
Last chance, Vance.
-我们走  -我要交易
- Let's go. - I want a deal.
他合作的条件
And in return for his cooperation,
除立即释放之外
aside from his immediate release,
我的委托人还要完全豁免权
my client wants full immunity.
警长  他意图贩毒是有证据的
Sergeant, we got him on Intent to Distribute,
他卖给了一名卧底警探
selling to an undercover police officer,
而你还想释放他
and you want to release him?
只要能把他的上线引出来就行
Just long enough to smoke out his source.
我们会追踪他的
He'll have a tracker on.
我不可能同意的
There's no way I can agree to that.
法官阁下  请您节哀
Your Honor, we are all so sorry for your loss.
我听说你来了
I heard you were here.
你们要和杀我女儿的凶手做交易
Are you guys making a deal with my daughter's killer?
我还没有签字
I haven't signed off on it.
跟您说  我没杀人
Just so you know, I'm not a killer, okay?
您女儿是个瘾君子
Your daughter was a junkie,
不论是我还是别人
and whether it was me or somebody else,
她总会找到毒品的
she was gonna find her pills.
这种阿片类毒品正在毁掉我们的国家
This opioid addiction is destroying our country.
所以如果非要做这种可耻的交易
So, if we have to make some unsavory deals...
那也只能这样了
So be it.
24小时  部分豁免权
24 hours, partial immunity.
听我说
Listen to me.
你今晚就把他约出来
You set up that meeting tonight.
不然这个交易作废  明白了吗
Or this deal is off the table. You understand?
还是没有弗兰克·巴雷特的踪影
Still no sign of Frank Barrett.
看来文斯和他的供应商决定不露面了
Vance and his supplier decided not to show up.
我们刚到  不过根据追踪器
Well, we just got here, but according to the tracker,
文斯还在他的房子里
Vance is still inside his house.
好吧  我们走
All right, come on.
凯文  你走前门  我们走后门
Kev, you take the front. We'll take the back.
明白
Got it.
安东尼奥
Antonio?
后门
Back door.
-开门  -明白
- Door. - Got it.
行动
Moving.
-有尸体  -收到
- Body. - Got it.
凯文  我们找到文斯了
Hey, Kev, we found Vance.
情况不妙
It's not good.
从后门强行闯入
Forced entry to the rear.
房子没被翻动
House wasn't tossed.
法医断定死亡时间为11点半
M.E. puts time of death at 11:30.
开了一枪
Single gun shot.
和邻居谈了  还没有线索
Talking to the neighbors. Nothing so far.
文斯的供货商有线索吗
Any intel on Vance's supplier?
没  只有他说的那些
No, just what he told us.
弗兰克·巴雷特  我们在查
Frank Barrett. We're looking into it.
鉴证科找到了一个鞋印
So, all crime techs found was one shoe print.
是11号的
It's a size 11.
被害人穿9号  所以可能是凶手的鞋
Victim was a size nine. So it could be the killer.
不过也有可能是送快递的
But it could also be the FedEx guy.
好吧  做个倒模
All right, get a cast.
-取证归档  -好的
- Put it into evidence. - Yep.
头部一枪致死
Got a kill shot to the head.
近距离开枪  没有打斗
Close range, no struggle.
这是处决
This was an execution.
问过鉴证科了  没有指纹
Spoke to the crime techs. There's no prints.
所以这个杀手还挺专业
So the guy was a professional.
子弹呢
Bullet?
我会送去做弹道检测的
I'll get it over to ballistics.
好  去问问邻居
All right, check the neighborhood
-找找安保录像吧  -行
- for security cameras, will you? - Yeah.
-老大  -怎么了
- Hey, boss? - Yeah.
我在搜他的柜子
Okay, I'm looking in the closet,
找到了至少一两万块钱
And there's at least 15 to 20K
藏在这边地板上的鞋盒子里
in a shoe box on the floor in there.
-让我看看  -好
- Give me a minute. - Yeah.
要我们送去入库吗
You want us to voucher it for you?
不用  我来办就行
No, I'll take care of it.
真的老大  我去办就行
Honestly, Boss, I can handle it.
警长  有发现了
Sarge, we found something.
-怎么了  -这是在壁炉里找到的
- What's up? - This was in the fire pit.
-是处方药瓶吗  -是
- Is that prescription bottles? - Yeah.
还有不少  看来他把它们都烧了
There's a bunch of them. Looks like he torched them.
不过标签还是能看出一点来
But you can still make out bits of the label.
羟考酮
OxyContin.
而且这些看上去好像都是一个人开的
And they all look like they were written by the same guy.
一个叫里维斯·梅西的医生
A Dr. Lewis Macy.
把它们送去化验室
Get them over to the lab.
看看能不能查到更多人
See if you can find some more names
去找这个里维斯·梅西聊一聊
and go talk to this Lewis Macy.
金·凯利  劳拉·亨德森
Kim Kelly. Laura Henderson.
这些人是你的病人吗
Are those patients of yours?
我不记得他们
Don't ring a bell.
你会开很多止痛处方药吗
Hey, do you write a lot of pain prescriptions?
-阿片类什么的  -当然不
- Opioids? - Oh, gosh, no.
我把这些东西叫做陷阱
I call those slippery slopes.
一片药就能让你永世不得翻身
One pill can take you right to the bottom.
也许你可以帮我们解释一下为什么这些病人的
Maybe you can help explain why we found Oxy prescriptions
羟考酮处方药都是你开的
for these patients written in your name.
这个简单
That's an easy one.
我的办公室半年前遭了小偷
My office was broken into six months ago.
他们偷走了我的电脑  零钱
They stole my computer, petty cash,
还有处方单
and my prescription pads.
你上报了吗
You reported this?
当然
Definitely.
是几个穿蓝色制服的警察来做的调查
A couple of your brothers in blue came to investigate.
显然这城里还有别的医生也遭了盗匪
Apparently other doctors in this city got robbed, too.
我们生活的这个年代可真是不太平
This is a real shame, the times we live in.
是啊
Yeah.
你认识一个叫弗兰克·巴雷特的人吗
Do you know a guy named Frank Barrett?
不认识
I don't.
-医生  -不好意思
- Doctor? - Ah, now if you'll excuse me,
我还有病人在等我
I do have patients waiting.
还有什么需要帮助的吗
Is there anything else I can help you with?
-谢谢  -谢了
- Thanks. - Thank you.
里维斯·梅西医生  家庭医生
Dr. Lewis Macy. Family doctor.
有两个孩子在上高中
Two kids in high school.
离异  没有前科
Divorce, no priors.
与死者文斯·威廉也没有明显关联
And no apparent connection to our DOA Vance Williams.
二者未通过电话和邮件
No phone calls. No E-mails.
这两个人从未在电子设备上有过任何交集
These two never crossed path electronically.
我问过抢劫组了
And I talked to robbery.
梅西医生确实上报过抢劫案
Dr. Macy did file a burglary report.
文斯被杀当晚他的不在场证明也没有问题
And his alibi for the night of Vance's murder checks out.
那天晚上在韦伯斯特预科学校有家长之夜
It was Parent Night at Webster Prep.
还有他穿九码的鞋
And he's a size nine.
和我们在案发现场发现的鞋印不相符
Not a match for the shoe print we found at the crime scene.
不过我还是想看看这位医生的
Still, I wanna get a sneak and peek
经济状况
on the doctor's finances.
那个叫弗兰克·巴雷特的人呢
What about this Frank Barrett guy?
芝加哥总共有八个叫这名的  警长
There's eight Frank Barretts in Chicago, Sarge.
不过我猜肯定是那家叫烈火的酒吧的老板
But my money is on the one who runs this bar called Blazes.
文斯·威廉以前在那里工作
That's where Vance Williams used to work.
我们在处方药瓶上找到的其他两个人
And two of the names we found on the prescription bottles
也有一个共同点
have one thing in common.
他们以前都曾在烈火酒吧工作
They both used to work at Blazes.
好  那我们就去抓他个把柄
All right, so let's get some dirt on him,
把他抓起来
then scoop him up.
你是弗兰克·巴雷特吗
Frank Barrett?
-我认识你们吗  -芝加哥警署
- Do I know you? - Chicago PD.
我们想和你聊聊你的一位员工
We wanted to talk to you about one of your employees,
文斯·威廉
Vance Williams.
他现在不在我这儿干了
Oh, yeah. He's a former employee.
我的经理跟我说了他发生了什么事
My manager told me what happened to him last night.
这个城市可真是不太平啊
This freaking city, huh?
你知不知道是谁杀的他
Do you have any idea who killed him?
不知道  他不过是曾经在我手下干活而已
No idea, he's just some guy who used to work for me.
文斯在倒卖非法阿片类药物
So, Vance was pushing illegal opiods.
我们也知道其他牵涉其中的人
We also know some other people in the ring,
他们都有一个共同点
and the one thing they all have in common--
就是都在你手下干过活
They've all worked for you.
你是觉得我和这件事有关
Oh, you think that I got something to do with this?
你是老板不是吗
You are the boss, right?
这又不是教堂  这只是一酒吧
It's not a church, man. It's a bar.
是啊  你昨晚在哪里
Yeah. Where were you last night?
在我的酒吧里
I was at my bar.
一直到关门
Till close.
听着  文斯发生的事是个悲剧
Look, it's tragic what happened to Vance,
但那和我没有关系
but I had nothing to do with it.
如果你们问够了的话
So if you guys are done fishing here,
我就先走了  我还得去上班
you'll excuse me. I have to get to work.
一个酒保竟然能开这么好的车
That's a nice ride for a bartender.
是酒吧老板
Bar owner.
在芝加哥卖酒还是挺挣钱的
A man can make a good living selling booze in Chicago.
不如我们也去一趟酒吧吧
Why don't we take a ride to the bar?
-查查他的不在场证明  -好
- Check out his alibi? - Mmm-hmm.
查到什么了
All right, what have you got?
我们在巴雷特的手机上安装了捕获追踪装置
We have the Trap and Trace on Barrett's phone.
如我们所想  巴雷特刚和
Like we hoped, Barrett made a phone call
霍斯特德和厄普顿说完话之后就打了电话
30 seconds after he talked to Halstead and Upton.
号码绝对是芝加哥的
Yeah, it's definitely a Chicago number,
但你们绝对不会相信这个号码是谁的
but you're not gonna believe who it belongs to.
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD.
介意我们进来吗
Mind if we come in?
快过来  这边
All right, come on. Over here.
-你们想干什么  -他在哪里
- What do you want? - Where is he?
-谁  什么  -看着我
- Who, what? - Hey, look at me.
-他在哪里  -安东尼奥
- Where is he? - Antonio?
怎么回事
What's this?
坐下  我正好也想问你
Sit down. We have the same question.
弗兰克·巴雷特刚刚给你打过电话
You just got a call from Frank Barrett.
对啊  弗兰克是我表弟
Yeah. Frank's my cousin.
文斯·威廉案的证据文件夹
The Vance Williams evidence folder.
我要做案件报告
I'm doing the case report.
我想再检查一遍证据
I wanna double-check evidence,
做做对照  好确保我没漏掉什么
cross reference to make sure I don't leave anything out.
这么专业啊
Like a real detective.
有没有什么金钱收据被收入了证据
Was there any money vouchered into evidence?
-里面有列吗  -没有
- Is there any listed there? - No.
那不就得了
There's your answer.
为什么带我过来  我什么都没做
Why am I here? I didn't do anything.
别担心  宝贝  都是误会
Don't worry, baby. It's all a mistake.
两间审讯室都空着吗
Both interview rooms clear?
是的  我们刚把新的亚麻布放进去
Yeah, we just put in fresh linens.
好的  她进一号  医生进二号
All right, her in one, Doc in two.
等等  我们能不能一起做笔录
Wait, is there any way we can do this together?
不能这么操作
That's not how this works.
你不能想想办法吗
Can't you do something?
-我在做案件报告  -好
- I'm on the case report. - Good.
要我们送去入库吗
You want us to voucher it for you?
不用  我来办就行
No,I'll take care of it.
真的老大  我去办就行
Honestly, Boss, I can handle it.
帮帮忙  医生
Now help me out here, Doc.
我只想搞清楚事情的来龙去脉
Just trying to fit some pieces together.
所以弗兰克·巴雷特是你表兄弟
So Frank Barrett is your cousin?
是的  我妈妈那边的亲戚
Yeah, that's right. On my mother's side.
安德瑞·斯科特是你女朋友
And Andrea Scott is your girlfriend?
-是的  -好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
她很不在状态啊  她在服用阿片类药物吗
She was pretty out of it. Is she doing opioids?
不是  她有医用大麻的合法处方
No, she has a legal prescription for medical marijuana.
-你帮她开的吗  -用来治她的偏头痛
- You write it for her? - It's for her migraines.
懂了
Oh, got it.
所以你和表弟弗兰克
Okay, so you and cousin Frank
是合法阿片类药物的生意搭档
are partners in an illegal opioid business.
不是  我已经跟你们说过有人偷了
No, I already told you somebody stole
-我的处方笺  -停
- my prescription pads. - Stop.
你骗了我们
You lied to us.
你说你不知道弗兰克·巴雷特是谁
You said you didn't know who Frank Barrett was.
我很紧张
I was nervous.
我不想说什么对我表弟不利的话
I didn't wanna say anything against my cousin.
但他没有贩毒  我只能这么说
But he's not a drug pusher, I'll tell you that much.
行了  玩这种良家医生的把戏
All right, listen. This mild-mannered doctor shtick?
你还是算了把
You're gonna have to come off it.
你在说...
What're you--
因为你跟两件谋杀案有关
Because you're connected to two murders.
你写错了处方
And you wrote the fraudulent scripts
害死了威尔斯法官的女儿
that killed the daughter of Judge Wells.
我没有
I didn't.
要么是你  要么是你表弟杀了文斯·威廉
And either you or your cousin shot Vance Williams.
我真的不知道这个人是谁
I have no idea who this man is.
是吗
Really?
因为我们在他家发现了
'Cause we found Oxy at his place
用你写的处方买到的羟考酮
from prescriptions that you wrote.
我觉得是你表弟拖你下水的
Now, I think your cousin got you into all this.
如果你想自保
If you wanna get out of it, hey...
你得帮我们抓你表弟
You gotta give us your cousin.
等等  我没明白
Wait, I'm not following.
我们需要你带窃听器
We need you to wear a wire.
让巴雷特说出他的阿片生意
Get Barrett to talk about his opioid dealings.
对不起  我做不到
I'm sorry, I could never do that.
好吧  那你就只能一个人扛了
All right, fine. You'll take the full ride alone.
怎么可以这样
That's crazy.
我说了  他们偷了我的处方笺
Like I said, they stole my prescription pads.
你真要坚持这么说吗
You really gonna hang onto that?
-我说的是事实  -我们问完了
- I'm telling you the truth. - We're done here.
从你怎么认识里维斯说起
Start with how you know Lewis.
我  我在夜店认识的里维斯
I, uh, I met Lewis at a club.
然后顺理成章
And then one thing led to another.
你不介意年龄差吗
The age difference didn't deter you?
我可能还是有恋父情结
I guess I still have daddy issues.
你有教唆未遂的前科
You have a prior for solicitation.
不是这样的
That's not what this is.
-我喜欢他  -好
- I like him. - That's great.
你跟弗兰克·巴雷特是什么关系
What's your relationship with Frank Barrett?
我只见过他几次
I only met him a few times.
他  他是里维斯的表弟  我只知道这个
He's--He's Lewis' cousin. That's all I know.
你吸毒多久了
How long you been using?
这是老疤
Those are old.
我们可以帮你
We can help you.
但我们得知道你的爱好有多不好
But we need to know how bad your habit is.
我只是一天吃一两片药
I just take a pill or two a day.
仅此而已
That's it.
拜托  我  其它的我什么都不知道
Please, I--I don't know anything else.
安德瑞  我觉得你知道
Andrea, I think you do know something.
你越早告诉我们你知道的事
And the sooner you tell us what you know,
就可以越早离开这里
the sooner you can go.
里维斯  今天有点奇怪
Lewis... he was acting strange today.
-他说为什么了吗  -没有
- Did he say why? - No.
但他一接到那通电话  我就知道是弗兰克
But when he got the call, I knew that it was from Frank.
然后里维斯跟他说
And then Lewis told him
警察也在问他问题
that the police were asking him questions, too.
然后他就开始慌了
And then he started freaking out.
然后警察就来了
And then the cops came.
所以巴雷特从梅西医生那里拿处方
So Barrett got prescriptions from Dr. Macy.
然后他给了文斯
Then he gave them to Vance.
文斯找人分销药物
Vance got the runners, distributed the pills.
巴雷特把自己排除在外了
Barrett sealed himself off.
现在  没有文斯
Now, without Vance,
唯一能拿下巴雷特的办法就是通过梅西
the only way to Barrett is through Macy.
他什么都不说
And he's not talking.
好吧  那安德瑞呢
All right, what about Andrea?
我们查了安德瑞的电话
Well, we dumped Andrea's phone.
目前没有她和巴雷特的直接联系
And right now, there's no obvious connection to her and Barrett.
我们确切知道的是她有瘾
What we do know is she has a serious habit.
把她关起来的话她肯定很难熬
She's gonna be sweating it out in lock-up,
想要过把瘾
looking for a fix.
那就能解释梅西家的羟考酮了
That explains the Oxy we found at Macy's apartment.
是的  你知道我们还发现了什么吗
Yeah, you know what else we found?
医生的情书  便利贴情书
Love notes from the doctor. Post-It notes.
"安德瑞  你是我所能想象到的所有欢愉"
"Andrea, you're every pleasure I've ever imagined."
"无论我们在一起多久
"No matter how much we're together,
我都不能满足"
I can never get enough of you."
那够了  我们找到重点了
Then that's it. We got him.
医生恋爱了
The doctor's in love.
我们可以利用她让他供认
And we use her to make him flip.
这是他的弱点
This is where he's vulnerable.
我们尽可能地利用
We squeeze as tight as we can.
把安德瑞放了  监视她
Cut Andrea loose. Keep eyes on her.
找到切实可用的东西
Find something actionable.
我一直在等你的电话
You know, I've been waiting for your call.
开玩笑吗  要在这里和我说吗
Are you kidding me right now? You're gonna talk to me here?
我看了看表
You know, according to my timepiece,
你还剩4个小时
you've got about four hours left.
我一直都很忙
Yeah, well I've been busy.
给你的钱  放在那里了吗
You plant that seed I gave you?
没有  把2万块放在那里太不容易了
No, all right? It's not easy to plant 20K, okay?
太多人在看着
There's too many eyes.
过来
Come here.
和我说话时摘下墨镜
remove your glasses when you talk to me.
天呐  他把钱拿了  是吗
Sweet Jesus, he took it, didn't he?
-不  没有  -别骗我
- No, that's not what happened. - Don't you lie to me.
-我没骗你  -那钱在哪里
- I'm not lying to you. - Then where's the money?
我需要更多时间  好吗
I need more time, all right?
我需要更多时间去放
I need more time to plant it.
我在等另一个机会
I'm waiting for another chance.
我觉得鱼已经被叉上了
I think the harpoon is already in the whale.
时间不等人
Time is ticking.
明天6点  你要么把钱带来
6:00 p.m. Tomorrow, you bring me the cash,
要么把博伊特拿走的证据给我
or proof that Voight took it.
说完了
We're done.
不
No!
求你了
Please, please!
-珍  -嗨
- Hey, Jen. - Hey.
谢谢你过来
Hey, thanks for coming.
-给你点了白葡萄酒  -谢谢
- Hey, I got you the white wine. - Thank you.
很高兴你打来  没想到会有你的消息
Glad you called. I wasn't expecting to hear from you.
知道吗  打给你不是为了那事
yeah, you know what? I didn't actually call about that.
我需要些建议
I need some advice.
没问题  有麻烦了吗
Sure. Are you in trouble?
我有个朋友
Well, I've got this friend.
也是个警察
Who's also a cop.
他妹妹醉驾
And, uh, his sister got a DUI.
妹妹的儿子当时也在车上
And her son was in the car.
惹上了事
Gonna be a mess.
我朋友搞定了这事
And my friend, he took care of it.
问题是  上面的人
The problem is, a white shirt--
发现了这事
he found out about it.
现在朋友一团糟
And now my friend's getting all jammed up.
我想知道  他面临的
I'm just wondering what kind of punishment
会是怎样的刑罚
he might be looking at.
伪造报告违反了第14条法案
Well, falsifying a report is a Rule 14 violation.
肯定是重罪
It's a straight felony.
而且还有上面的人指认他
Plus with a white shirt gunning for him,
你的朋友会面临5年的监禁
I'd say your friend is looking at five years in prison.
好的
Okay.
好严厉
Ouch.
这是一个改造过的新世界
It's the new world of reform.
每个人都想让警察完蛋
Everybody wants to bury a cop.
是啊
Yeah.
我们逮捕了你的女朋友
We arrested your girlfriend.
她在西区买海洛因
She was buying heroin on the west side.
她很努力在戒毒
She's been trying to wean herself off.
她只需要回戒毒所
She just needs to go back to rehab.
如果你开始合作
Well, you can make that happen
那是没问题的
if you start cooperating.
我知道你什么意思
I know what you're trying to do.
你表弟是个经销毒品的
Your cousin is a drug pusher.
他谋杀了我们知道的一个人
He killed one man we know of,
还在勒索你
and he's extorting you.
现在 你可以保他
Now, you can save him,
或者你女朋友
or you can save her.
遇到安德瑞
When I met Andrea,
让我活了过来
that's when I came back to life.
我总算是第一次为自己做了些什么
For the first time I was finally doing something for me.
但最紧要的是
And then on top of everything else,
我得支付离婚费用
I had a divorce to pay for.
所以你去找了表弟弗兰克  对吗
Okay, so you reached out to your cousin Frank, yeah?
弗兰克总说需要什么的时候找他
Frank always told me if I ever needed anything...
我还不起贷款
I couldn't pay the loan back.
所以他才要我写处方
That is when he asked for the prescriptions.
接着我就没办法抽身了
Then I didn't know how to get out.
安德瑞会怎样
What about Andrea?
你把弗兰克交给我们
Listen, you give us Frank,
安德瑞就没事了  我保证
Andrea walks. You have my word.
总有一天  我会摆脱这个负担
One day, I'm gonna have this darn monkey off my back,
安德瑞和我会在一起
and Andrea and I are gonna be together.
这是一个传输设备
This is a transmitting device.
和普通电话一样
Works like a regular phone.
还可以接电话
You can still receive calls.
按这个按钮两次   就可以用了
You press this button twice, you're ready to rock.
我不知道能否做到
I don't know if I can do this.
弗兰克是我的家人
Frank is my family.
我们一起长大
We grew up together,
现在我要背后捅他一刀
and now I'm gonna stab him in the back.
不  我不是这样的人
No, no, this isn't who I am.
你知道你自己的
You know who you are.
你是一个做错了选择的人
You're a guy with no good options.
所以你得接受
So you gotta deal with it.
我是做错了  可这样也是错的
What I did was wrong. This is also wrong.
有的时候负负得正
Yeah, well, sometimes two wrongs make a right.
按这个按钮两次
Press this button twice.
走吧
Let's go.
看到医生的时候说一声
Let me know when you got eyes on the doctor.
看到了  在长凳边上
Yeah, we got him. He's by the bench.
还看到巴雷特了
Got eyes on Barrett, too.
穿了黑外套  蓝色牛仔裤
Black jacket, blue jeans.
现在走过来了
He's approaching right now.
收到
Copy that.
弗兰克
Frank.
为什么在这见面
Why'd you wanna meet here?
警察一直在外面转悠
cops have been poking around the bar.
怎么了  你想说什么
So, what's up? What'd you wanna talk about?
关于警察
About the cops.
你说过不会有事的
You said nothing was gonna happen.
什么事都没有
Nothing has happened.
我们去走走
Let's go take a walk.
-去哪  -随便走走  来
- Where? - Eh, we'll just walk. Come on.
好的  他们走了
All right, they're on the move.
东南方向
Southeast.
你要干什么  里维斯
So, what do you really want, Lewis?
我很怕他们找到
Look, I'm scared they're going to find out.
找到什么
About what?
找到羟考酮药
About the Oxy pills.
你在说什么
What are you talking about, huh?
他们没有办法把事情联系到我们身上的
There's no way that they can connect anything to us.
这是完美的
It's perfect.
我们要做的就是守口如瓶
Look, all you gotta do is stick to the story.
文斯呢
What about Vance?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
走
Come on.
我们看到他们了
All right, hey, we got eyes.
你们退后一点  不要惊动他
I want you to hang back. We don't wanna heat this guy.
收到
Copy.
真是奇怪  里维斯
You know, that's strange, Lewis.
你刚才提到那个人
That person you're referring to,
我不记得告诉过你他的名字了
I don't remember telling you his name.
警察告诉我了文斯
The police told me about Vance.
警察吗
The police, huh?
你跟他们聊了多少次了
How many times you talk to them?
一两次吧
Once, twice.
到底是几次  一次还是两次
Well, which one is it? Once or twice?
不重要  你为什么杀了他
It doesn't matter. Why did you kill him?
你为什么要我承认我没做的事
Why are you trying to get me to admit to something i didn't do?
-我想知道  -什么
- I just wanna know. - Huh?
他们给你安窃听了吗
What, did they put a wire on you?
-没有  -你有窃听吗
- No. - You got a wire?
不  没有
No, God, no.
我们可以救他
We can pull him out.
等我的命令
Wait for my order.
警察买通你了吗  里维斯
Did the cops flip you, Lewis?
不  不是的
No, it's not like that.
弗兰克  弗兰克
Frank. Frank!
-弗兰克  -他们进入隧道了
- Frank! - They're going in the tunnel.
-弗兰克  -听我说
- Frank! - Hey, listen to me.
我不管我们是不是一家人
I don't care that we're family.
如果你跟警察交代了
If you ever say anything to the cops--
弗兰克  你他妈在干什么
Frank, what the hell are you doing?
我要拿这把枪打死你
I will shove this gun so far down your--
现在冲进去
Move in, now.
好的  大家上
All right, go, man. Go, go, go.
警长  梅西受伤  但是我们在了
Sarge, Macy's down, but we got him.
巴雷特从西边逃出了隧道
Barrett fled out the west side of the tunnel.
阿特沃特和厄普顿去追了
Atwater and Upton are in pursuit.
但他们应该没看到他
I do not believe that they have eyes.
我看到巴雷特了
I got eyes on Barrett.
他在公园的南边
He's at the south end of the park.
那里有非常多的孩子
You guys, there's a lot of kids around.
巴雷特有枪
Barrett is armed.
有太多的居民了  不能冒险
There's too many civilians to take any chances.
逮捕过程中要注意安全
Apprehend without incident.
那是一只斑马吗  好的
Hey, is that a zebra? Okay, great.
他上公交车了  289路
He's getting on the bus. The 289.
抱歉  今天怎么样
Sorry. How's it going?
谢谢
Thanks.
别轻举妄动  弗兰克
Nice and easy, Frank.
多亏了你表哥
Well, thanks to your cousin,
我们抓到你贩毒
we got you on drug trafficking,
并且因毒品杀害朱利安·威尔斯
narcotics induced homicide of Julianne Wells,
现在还有谋杀你的表哥
and now the murder-- or attempted murder--
或者谋杀未遂
of your cousin.
拜托  那个傻子去抢枪  走火了
Ah, come on. The idiot grabbed the gun and it went off.
我不会打他的
I wasn't gonna shoot him.
你还想辩解什么吗
Anything else you wanna say in your defense?
我打算让我的律师处理这件事
You know what? I think I'll let my lawyer handle that.
这是谋杀  兄弟
This is murder, bro.
文斯是你的中间人
Vance was your middle man.
你发现他要溜
You found out he was gonna roll.
你就杀了他
You killed him, too.
我可能和毒品交易有关
Look, I may have had something to do with the pills.
但是我和那个人的死一点关系都没有
But I had nothing to do with that guy's murder.
我们知道文斯和你约了见面
We know Vance set a meeting with you.
我们在现场还找到了你的鞋印
And we got your shoeprint at the scene.
11码
Size 11.
我是有一双11码的鞋
Yeah, I do have a size 11.
但是那个人死的时候我有不在场证明
But I also have an alibi for the night that guy was killed.
我们查了  你七点离开了烈火酒吧
And we checked it. You left Blazes at seven.
有非常多的时间作案
That's plenty of time to do this murder.
听着
Okay, look.
我整晚在那里是谎话
I lied about being there all night.
因为我在见一个医生
It's because I was meeting a doctor.
他叫弗洛
His name is Furlow.
丹尼尔·弗洛医生
Dr. Daniel Furlow.
我看他是不是方便搞药
I was seeing if he might wanna be in business.
我本来不想声张的
It's not exactly something I wanted to advertise.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
在哪里
Where was this?
在大使酒店
It was at the Ambassador Hotel.
你可以去查
And you can check that.
你还撒了什么谎
What else did you lie about?
你拿到什么把柄了
So, what have you got for me?
我想了很长时间
You know, I've thought a lot about this situation.
我计算过了
I've gone over all the math,
所有的可能性
all the possibilities.
然后我想到了一个办法
And I think I came to a conclusion.
去你妈的
Screw you.
感觉真不错
Oh, that feels good.
没错  去你妈的
Yeah, screw you.
你肯定数学不好
You know, you must be lousy at math,
因为你的答案错误了
because you got the exact wrong answer.
是  但你知道吗
Yeah, well, you know what?
只有这样我才能心安  所以
It's the only one I can live with, so--
你的家人呢
And what about your family?
博伊特就是我的家人
Voight is my family.
你好像就是不懂这一点
That's what you don't seem to understand.
他们都是我的家人
They're all my family.
我不会向你这种人出卖他们
And I'm not gonna give them up for the likes of you.
你这一步走错了  孩子
Not a bridge you wanna burn, son.
我觉得自己做得再对不过了
No, it is a bridge that I wanna blow the hell up.
你和你那些高尚的狗屁
You with all your high-minded BS.
你的优越感
Your superiority.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
你之所以这么想扳倒博伊特
I mean, the only reason that you wanna get Voight so bad
是因为你知道自己连他的一半都不如
is because you realize you're not half the man he is.
我告诉你  你永远都不如他
And I'm here to tell you you never will be.
鲁塞克警官
Officer Ruzek...
享受你当警察的最后一天吧
Enjoy your last day as a cop.
我会的
I will.
抱歉这么晚过来
Hey, sorry for the late hour.
没事
It's all right.
我也睡不着
I haven't been sleeping.
我是有好消息
Oh, well, I do have some good news.
什么
Yeah?
抓到弗兰克·巴雷特了
Busted Frank Barrett.
助理检察官要以因毒谋杀朱利安的罪名起诉他
ASA's charging him with the drug induced homicide of Julianne.
谢谢你  汉克
Thank you, Hank.
至少让我有点安慰了
There's some cold comfort in that.
我很高兴  看这个
I'm glad. Look at this.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你还记得那次我们在沃巴什街追捕那些
You remember that time we chased those robbery suspects
抢劫嫌犯  然后把他们困在E1铁轨那里吗
across Wabash, trapped them under the El tracks?
记得  督察报告说
Yeah, the inspector wrote me up
我没带警帽
for not wearing my crown cap.
你的配枪还有吗
You still got your service revolver?
没有了
Uh, no, no.
-丢了  -丢了
- I lost it. - Lost it?
-对  -就那么消失了吗
- Yeah. - Just disappeared, huh?
本来放在一个盒子里
Well, you know, it got put into a box,
后来有一天就不见了
and then one day it was gone.
真遗憾
Well, that's too bad.
记得吗  那种枪用的是很特别的357子弹
They had that special ammo for those 357s, remember?
-那是很久以前的事了  -是
- It was a long time ago. - Yeah, well...
我之所以想到它  是因为弹道检测结果出了
The reason I think of it is we just got the ballistics back.
文斯·威廉是被38口径的凹弹杀害的
Vance Williams was killed with a .38 caliber hollow-point.
就是我们当时的配枪用的子弹
The same ammo we used in our service revolvers.
而且
And the thing is...
只有警察有那种子弹
Only cops got those bullets.
1994年那种子弹停产
And they stopped making them in 1994.
跟你从警署辞职的时间一样
Which is the same year you stopped being a policeman.
你的鞋子大概是11码  汤米
You about a size 11, Tommy.
我不知道你想说什么  汉克
I'm not sure what you're getting at, Hank.
你告诉我巴雷特是谋杀嫌疑人
You told me that Barrett was good for the murder.
我之前以为是他  不过
Yeah, well, I thought he was, but...
他的不在场证明是真的
His alibi checked out.
他并不在现场
He wasn't there.
汤米
Tommy.
汤米  你当警察的时候我很了解你
Tommy, I knew you when you were a cop.
我知道你的本事
I know what you're capable of.
我知道看着杀害了自己孩子的
And I know what it's like to look into the eyes
人的眼睛  是什么感觉
of the person that killed your child.
如果你仔细调查  汉克
If you look really closely, Hank,
你应该会发现
I think you'll see
没有任何物证把我和这起谋杀联系起来
that there's no physical evidence to tie me to this murder.
即使你想立案
And even if you try to make a case,
我也在这里做了30年的警察和法官
I've been a judge and a cop in this town for 30 years.
我结交了很多朋友
All the friends that I've made?
就是一支军队
It's an army.
汤米  我只是说我知道真相
Tommy, I'm just saying I know what happened.
我知道
I know.
没有你想的那么好受  对吧
Doesn't feel as good as you think it will, does it?
我需要点东西
I need something.
尽管说
I'm listening.
伙计
Hey, man.
我得去见一个线人
I gotta go meet a C.I.
你跟我一起去吧
I could use the back up.
要我叫上阿特沃特吗
You want me to call in Atwater?
不用  就你和我
No, you and me.
就跟以前一样
Just like the old days.
好吧  走
All right, yeah.
-我喜欢  -嗯
- I like that. - Yeah.
记得我们第一次见面的时候吗
Remember the first time we met?
-在警校里  -对
- At the Academy? - That's right.
当时你揪着你的指导员
You were on top of your instructor.
那是人质演习
It was a hostage drill.
我们应该解除他的武器
We were supposed to disarm him.
是啊  你揍了他
Yeah, you beat him up.
反正我解除他的武器了
I disarmed him.
你一直跟我儿子一样
You know, you've always been like a son to me.
我们不是要去南边吗
I thought we were going to the south side.
刚改变了地点
Yeah, we just changed the venue.
就是那个线人
That's the C.I.
嗯
Yeah.
走吧
Come on.
我们要见的是谁  老埃
Who are we meeting, Al?
老埃
Al.